## ASHLEY ANN GUAN

# Thrift Shop Sales Assistant

### CONTACT

\$\(\&\) +(65) 81005998

### **EDUCATION**

# FOOD BUSINESS MANAGEMENT (CULINARY ARTS)

Singapore Institute of Technology/Culinary Institute of America

Aug 2021 - Sep

2022

# DIPLOMA IN FOOD SCIENCE & NUTRITION

Temasek Polytechnic

2018 - 2021

GCE 'O' LEVELS

Pasir Ris Crest Secondary School

2014 - 2017

#### HOBBIES

Sewing

Crocheting

Baking

Cooking

Photography

Videography

#### REFERENCES

Lena Tan, Owner of Thrift Label

+(65) 96571263

∠ Lena@thriftlabel.com.sg

#### ABOUT ME

I am a curious person and have the drive and passion in learning new trades. I have worked mostly in the F&B industry, developing teamwork, problem-solving and effective communication. I enjoy sewing and crocheting in my leisure time, adding a few pieces to my own wardrobe. I enjoy visiting art and historical exhibitions during my free time!

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# THRFIT SHOP SALES ASSISTANT AND SOCIAL MEDIA MANAGER

Thrift Label

### Oct 2022 - Present

- Cashiering
- Restocking of items
- Maintaining the cleanliness of the shop
- Promoting the shop via TikTok and Instagram

#### PREP COOK

Bistro G

#### May 2022 - July 2022

- Assist in the daily mise en place (food preparation)
- · Assisted in plating and presentation of food
- Maintained the cleanliness of workstations

#### INTERN

Nouri

### Dec 2021

- Shadowed under the Garde Manger (Appetiser) Chef
- Assisted in the daily mise en place for the Garde Manger Station
- Stationed to Garde Manger during lunch and dinner service

#### CAKE PRODUCTION ASSISTANT

ABR Holdings Limited

#### June & July 2021

- Assisted the supervisors to achieve the various production targets
- Ensured the production plant operates in compliance with the Operating Level Program Standards, and local authorities regulations
- Enforced the in-house housekeeping and cleaning schedule
- Ensured the production of cakes is within specifications
- Ensured smooth running of the operation process

#### **INTERNSHIP**

Temasek Polytechnic

### June 2020 - Sep 2020

- Researched resistant starch content in various types of rice and factors which would increase
  the content.
- Conducted experiments based on research and summarized a report on experimental findings.
- Reported results in Microsoft Excel with Megazyme: Resistant Starch Assay Kit during scheduled experiment days

#### PART-TIME FOOD SERVICE WORKER

Boost Juice International

#### Oct 2019 - Feb 2020

- · -Attained Food and Beverage Safety and Hygiene Policies and Procedures Certificate
- · -Handled Customers' orders while cashiering
- -Maintained basic housekeeping in store

### NOTABLE ACHIEVEMENTS & AWARDS

EDUSAVE CERTIFICATE FOR ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT 2015, 2016, 2019

EDUSAVE AWARD FOR ACHIEVEMENT, GOOD LEADERSHIP AND SERVICE (EAGLES)
2018

NATIONAL YOUTH ACHIEVEMENT AWARD - BRONZE & SILVER 2016 & 2017

**EDUSAVE CHARACTER AWARD** 

2016

**EDUSAVE SCHOLARSHIP** 

2014